<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="app_name">Alforqan</string>
    <string name="testString">&quot; السلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاتهالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته السلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاتهالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاتهالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته Text\tالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاتهالسلام عليكم و رحمة الله و بركاته&quot;</string>
    <string name="ayarepeatenterylabel">تكرار الآية</string>
    <string name="grouprepeatenterylabel">تكرار المجموعة</string>
    <string name="about_string">عن البرنامج</string>
    <string name="preferences_string">إعدادات التلاوة</string>
    <string name="back_string">عودة</string>

</resources>